

Skills

Ability to Work in a Team

Computer Skills

Adobe Illustrator

Microsoft Excel

Microsoft PowerPoint

Microsoft Office

Knowledge of MS Office

Customer Service

Administrative Skills

Languages

Chinese

Hobbies

English

Malay

Travelling

Profile

I am a senior office administrator offering 6 years of experience facilitating operations in different types office settings. Leverages communication and management skills for efficient office operation. Organized and attentive professional with demonstrated talent in administrative support. Moreover, I also have outstanding knowledge of effective office coordination with commitment to effective administrative collaboration.

Employment History

Senior Office Administrator, Premium Automobile PTE LTD (Audi Service center), Singapore

June 2014 — Present

- Provided administrative support, including processing purchase orders, service contracts and financial reports.
- Managed office inventory by restocking supplies and placing purchase orders to maintain adequate stock levels.
- Applied necessary support packs to SAP (supplier side)
- Entered invoices requiring payment and disbursed amounts via check, electronic transfer or bank draft to customer
- Prepared packages for shipment (packing list and M3 list), pickup and courier services for prompt delivery to customers (oversea) Export.
- Maintained accurate, current and compliant financial records by monitoring and addressing variances.
- Developed and updated spreadsheets and databases to track, analyze and report on performance and sales data.
- Worked with supervisors and management to maintain status reports and update information for client projects.

Customer Service Assistant, Hup Seng Trading (Wholesales Food Industry), Malaysia

October 2011 - March 2014

- Counted cash drawers and deposits, checked supplies and completed any other required opening or closing task to facilitate smooth team operations.
- Addressed customer complaints and mitigated dissatisfaction by employing timely and effective solutions.

- Conferred with customers about concerns with products or services to resolve problems and drive sales.
- Established and prepared accurate customers accounts to complete new purchases.
- Promoted company brand and unique offerings through personalized customer service.
- Educated customers on promotions to enhance sales.
- Maintained accurate and current customer account data with manual forms processing and digital information updates.

Education

Malaysian Higher School Certificate (STPM), SMK TUN HUSSIEN ONN, Malaysia

June 2008 - December 2009

- Mathematics (Major) Pass
- General education Pass
- Business Administration Pass
- Economic Pass

Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM), SMK JALAN MENGIKBOL, Kluang

January 2004 — December 2007

- Science Academics
- · Pass all the subject

Current and Expected salary (SGD)

January 2020 — Present

- Current basic salary: \$ 2,800
- Expected basic salary: \$ 3,000 to \$ 3,500

Courses

Mental arithmetic, Best mental arithmetic Center(Malaysia)

February 2000 — February 2001